siamrealestate.com 2018-12-27

# Privacy

**Privacy Policy**

**www.siamrealestate.com**

**Who we are**

Siam Real Estate, trading under Siam Real Estate Phuket Co. Ltd and Siam Real Estate Bangkok Co. Ltd. (SRE)

We are a company incorporated in Thailand whose registered office’s 2/42 Moo 4, Viset Road, Rawai, Phuket, Thailand, 83130 (registered with company number 0835546000743) and 6th Floor, The Trendy Building, Sukhumvit Soi 13, Bangkok, 10110 (registered with company number 0105560064831)

**What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?**

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, phone number or other details to help you with your experience.

**When do we collect information?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to a newsletter, fill out a form or enter information on our site.

**How do we use your information?**

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:

      • To personalize your experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.

      • To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.

      • To follow up with them after correspondence (live chat, email or phone inquiries)

**How do we protect your information?**

Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible.

We use regular Malware Scanning.

Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. 

We implement a variety of security measures when a user places an order to maintain the safety of your personal information.

All transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our servers.

**Do we use 'cookies'?**

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

**We use cookies to:**

      • Understand and save user's preferences for future visits.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since browser is a little different, look at your browser's Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

If you turn cookies off, It won't affect the user's experience.

**Third-party disclosure**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information unless we provide users with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or serving our users, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release information when it's release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property or safety. 

However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

**Third-party links**

We do not include or offer third-party products or services on our website.

**Google**

Google's advertising requirements can be summed up by Google's Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. 

https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en 

**We have implemented the following:**

      • Google Display Network Impression Reporting

      • Demographics and Interests Reporting

We, along with third-party vendors such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and other ad service functions as they relate to our website. 

**Opting out:**  
Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative Opt Out page or by using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.

**How does our site handle Do Not Track signals?**

We honor Do Not Track signals and Do Not Track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place. 

**Does our site allow third-party behavioral tracking?**

It's also important to note that we do not allow third-party behavioral tracking

**Fair Information Practices**

The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.

**In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:**

We will notify you via email within 7 business days

We will notify the users via in-site notification within 7 business days

We also agree to the Individual Redress Principle which requires that individuals have the right to legally pursue enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or government agencies to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.

**CAN SPAM Act**

The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.

**We collect your email address in order to:**

      • Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions

      • Market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our clients after the original transaction has occurred.

**To be in accordance with CANSPAM, we agree to the following:**

      • Not use false or misleading subjects or email addresses.

      • Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way.

      • Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters.

      • Monitor third-party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.

      • Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly.

      • Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email.

**  
If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email us at**

      • Follow the instructions at the bottom of each email.

and we will promptly remove you from **ALL** correspondence.

**Applicable law**

In the event of any dispute, controversy or claim arising out of or relating to the use of the Service of the company, you agree that such dispute, controversy and claim shall be governed by the Kingdom of Thailand laws and settled by Thai courts.  

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below.

www.siamrealestate.com

2/42, Moo 4, Viset Road

Rawai, Phuket 83130 ,Thailand
